gcflearnfree.org 2008-06-17

# GCFLearnFree.org: Privacy Statement

Privacy protection is important at GCFLearnFree.org®, and we want you to know that we make sure that your personal information remains confidential. Please take a moment to read the following statement to learn how we handle your personal information. 

GCFLearnFree.org is administered by Goodwill Industries of Eastern North Carolina, Inc, a 501(c)(3), tax-exempt organization. Our mission is to "provide an environment for people to improve the quality of their lives through employment and learning opportunities with a focus on persons with disabilities."

####  Information Release

GCFLearnFree.org recognizes the importance of an individual's privacy and does not release individual records to outside agencies for any reason. Users have access to their own class records and are responsible for their release. Learner records are stored in a secure database for a minimum of seven years. 

####  User Feedback

At times, GCFLearnFree.org will use user feedback in learner surveys, site feedback email, and class discussion board posts to enhance our website and materials. We do not disclose any personal information about the individuals and we refer to them anonymously. 

####  Email Communication

We may use third-party software to manage and mail our email newsletters and announcements. Any third-party software we use will maintain our same strict privacy standards so that you can rest assured that your private information stays confidential. At any time, you can subscribe or unsubscribe to our email list, which contains information about the learning opportunities at GCFLearnFree.org. Your subscription can be managed by signing into the site and clicking the _My Profile_ link. 

####  Cookies

Like many websites, GCFLearnFree.org uses 'cookie' technology, in the form of session and stored cookies. A cookie is a piece of data that enables a website to send information to your browser. By doing this, the cookie can collect information to personalize your experience, count page hits, see what pages are most popular, allow you to access your special links and class-related material, and help us study traffic patterns to better serve you on our site. 

GCFLearnFree.org does not collect any personal information outside of what users already provide when they create a user account with GCFLearnFree.org and only uses this information to enhance users’ experiences on our website.
